He had money but didn't lend it to me
Made me borrow from loan sharks
He knew I needed the secret feed
But refused to sell it to me
Why shouldn't I hate him
You
You're just being unreasonable
You bite the hand that feeds you
This kind of person
It's useless being nice to him
Stop acting so righteous
I tried nicely to buy feed from you before
But you wouldn't sell
Now I'm not buying
Your feed recipe
Jason has memorized it all
Now he's working for me
Within a week
My forest frogs will outweigh yours
Then Walter's ten-million order
Will be mine
Great talents are common
But those who recognize them are rare
A great talent like me
Has finally found a visionary like Daniel
Wait till I help Daniel snatch your order
You'll realize how short-sighted you are
Dumb and dumber
Perfect match
Keep talking tough
Jason
Let's go
Lewes what if the recipe
Don't worry
They can't steal it
Your judgment
Is still as bad as always
Always treating trash like treasure
Jason
Didn't you say you knew
Lewes's feed recipe
It's almost been a week
Why are the frogs getting thinner
Well
That's impossible
I followed the recipe exactly
Then why aren't they gaining weight
Do you actually have Lewes's recipe
Boss I remember now
I
Seem to be missing one ingredient
What ingredient
I don't know
Zong Jiajie